<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<enums>
	<enum dbus_type="i" name="role">
		<item name="atspi_role_invalid" value="0">
			<description>
				 A role indicating an error condition, such as
							uninitialized Role data.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_accelerator_label" value="1">
			<description>
				 Object is a label indicating the keyboard
							accelerators for the parent.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_alert" value="2">
			<description>
				 Object is used to alert the user about something.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_animation" value="3">
			<description>
				 Object contains a dynamic or moving image of some
							kind.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_arrow" value="4">
			<description>
				 Object is a 2D directional indicator.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_calendar" value="5">
			<description>
				 Object contains one or more dates, usually arranged
							into a 2D list.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_canvas" value="6">
			<description>
				 Object that can be drawn into and is used to trap
							events.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_check_box" value="7">
			<description>
				 A choice that can be checked or unchecked and
							provides a separate indicator for the current state.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_check_menu_item" value="8">
			<description>
				 A menu item that behaves like a check box. See
							ATSPI_ROLE_CHECK_BOX.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_color_chooser" value="9">
			<description>
				 A specialized dialog that lets the user choose a
							color.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_column_header" value="10">
			<description>
				 The header for a column of data.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_combo_box" value="11">
			<description>
				 A list of choices the user can select from.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_date_editor" value="12">
			<description>
				 An object which allows entry of a date.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_desktop_icon" value="13">
			<description>
				 An inconifed internal frame within a DESKTOP_PANE.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_desktop_frame" value="14">
			<description>
				 A pane that supports internal frames and
							 iconified versions of those internal frames.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_dial" value="15">
			<description>
				 An object that allows a value to be changed via rotating a
							 visual element, or which displays a value via such a rotating element.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_dialog" value="16">
			<description>
				 A top level window with title bar and a border.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_directory_pane" value="17">
			<description>
				 A pane that allows the user to navigate through
							 and select the contents of a directory.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_drawing_area" value="18">
			<description>
				 An object used for drawing custom user interface
							 elements.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_file_chooser" value="19">
			<description>
				 A specialized dialog that displays the files in
							 the directory and lets the user select a file, browse a different
							 directory, or specify a filename.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_filler" value="20">
			<description>
				 A object that fills up space in a user interface.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_focus_traversable" value="21">
			<description>
				 Don't use, reserved for future use.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_font_chooser" value="22">
			<description>
				 Allows selection of a display font.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_frame" value="23">
			<description>
				 A top level window with a title bar, border, menubar,
							 etc.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_glass_pane" value="24">
			<description>
				 A pane that is guaranteed to be painted on top of
							 all panes beneath it.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_html_container" value="25">
			<description>
				 A document container for HTML, whose children
							 represent the document content.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_icon" value="26">
			<description>
				 A small fixed size picture, typically used to decorate
							 components.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_image" value="27">
			<description>
				 An image, typically static.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_internal_frame" value="28">
			<description>
				 A frame-like object that is clipped by a desktop
							 pane.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_label" value="29">
			<description>
				 An object used to present an icon or short string in an
							 interface.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_layered_pane" value="30">
			<description>
				 A specialized pane that allows its children to be
							 drawn in layers, providing a form of stacking order.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_list" value="31">
			<description>
				 An object that presents a list of objects to the user and
							 allows the user to select one or more of them.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_list_item" value="32">
			<description>
				 An object that represents an element of a list.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_menu" value="33">
			<description>
				 An object usually found inside a menu bar that contains a
							 list of actions the user can choose from.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_menu_bar" value="34">
			<description>
				 An object usually drawn at the top of the primary
							 dialog box of an application that contains a list of menus the user can
							 choose from.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_menu_item" value="35">
			<description>
				 An object usually contained in a menu that presents
							 an action the user can choose.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_option_pane" value="36">
			<description>
				 A specialized pane whose primary use is inside a
							 dialog.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_page_tab" value="37">
			<description>
				 An object that is a child of a page tab list.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_page_tab_list" value="38">
			<description>
				 An object that presents a series of panels (or
							 page tabs), one at a time,through some mechanism provided by the
							 object.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_panel" value="39">
			<description>
				 A generic container that is often used to group objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_password_text" value="40">
			<description>
				 A text object uses for passwords, or other places
							 where the text content is not shown visibly to the user.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_popup_menu" value="41">
			<description>
				 A temporary window that is usually used to offer the
							 user a list of choices, and then hides when the user selects one of those
							 choices.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_progress_bar" value="42">
			<description>
				 An object used to indicate how much of a task has
							 been completed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_push_button" value="43">
			<description>
				 An object the user can manipulate to tell the
							 application to do something.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_radio_button" value="44">
			<description>
				 A specialized check box that will cause other
							 radio buttons in the same group to become unchecked when this one is
							 checked.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_radio_menu_item" value="45">
			<description>
				 Object is both a menu item and a "radio button".
							 See ATSPI_ROLE_RADIO_BUTTON.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_root_pane" value="46">
			<description>
				 A specialized pane that has a glass pane and a
							 layered pane as its children.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_row_header" value="47">
			<description>
				 The header for a row of data.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_scroll_bar" value="48">
			<description>
				 An object usually used to allow a user to
							 incrementally view a large amount of data by moving the bounds of a
							 viewport along a one-dimensional axis.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_scroll_pane" value="49">
			<description>
				 An object that allows a user to incrementally view
							 a large amount of information. Scroll pane objects are usually
							 accompanied by ATSPI_ROLE_SCROLL_BAR controllers, on which the
							 ATSPI_RELATION_CONTROLLER_FOR and ATSPI_RELATION_CONTROLLED_BY
							 reciprocal relations are set. See the GetRelationSet method.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_separator" value="50">
			<description>
				 An object usually contained in a menu to provide a
							 visible and logical separation of the contents in a menu.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_slider" value="51">
			<description>
				 An object that allows the user to select from a bounded range.
							 Unlike ATSPI_ROLE_SCROLL_BAR, ATSPI_ROLE_SLIDER objects need not control
							 'viewport'-like objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_spin_button" value="52">
			<description>
				 An object which allows one of a set of choices to
							 be selected, and which displays the current choice.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_split_pane" value="53">
			<description>
				 A specialized panel that presents two other panels
							 at the same time.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_status_bar" value="54">
			<description>
				 Object displays non-quantitative status information
							 (c.f. ATSPI_ROLE_PROGRESS_BAR)

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_table" value="55">
			<description>
				 An object used to repesent information in terms of rows
							 and columns.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_table_cell" value="56">
			<description>
				 A 'cell' or discrete child within a Table. Note:
							 Table cells need not have ATSPI_ROLE_TABLE_CELL, other
							 role values are valid as well.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_table_column_header" value="57">
			<description>
				 An object which labels a particular column
							 in a Table interface interface.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_table_row_header" value="58">
			<description>
				 An object which labels a particular row in a
							 Table interface. Table rows and columns may also be labelled via the
							 ATSPI_RELATION_LABEL_FOR/ATSPI_RELATION_LABELLED_BY relationships; see
							 the GetRelationSet method.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tearoff_menu_item" value="59">
			<description>
				 Object allows menu to be removed from menubar
							 and shown in its own window.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_terminal" value="60">
			<description>
				 An object that emulates a terminal.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_text" value="61">
			<description>
				 An interactive widget that supports multiple lines of text
							 and optionally accepts user input, but whose purpose is not to solicit user
							 input. Thus ATSPI_ROLE_TEXT is appropriate for the text view in a plain text
							 editor but inappropriate for an input field in a dialog box or web form. For
							 widgets whose purpose is to solicit input from the user, see ATSPI_ROLE_ENTRY
							 and ATSPI_ROLE_PASSWORD_TEXT. For generic objects which display a brief amount
							 of textual information, see ATSPI_ROLE_STATIC.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_toggle_button" value="62">
			<description>
				 A specialized push button that can be checked or
							 unchecked, but does not procide a separate indicator for the current
							 state.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tool_bar" value="63">
			<description>
				 A bar or palette usually composed of push buttons or
							 toggle buttons.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tool_tip" value="64">
			<description>
				 An object that provides information about another
							 object.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tree" value="65">
			<description>
				 An object used to repsent hierarchical information to the
							 user.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tree_table" value="66">
			<description>
				 An object that presents both tabular and
							 hierarchical info to the user.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_unknown" value="67">
			<description>
				 The object contains some accessible information,
							 but its role is not known.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_viewport" value="68">
			<description>
				 An object usually used in a scroll pane, or to
							 otherwise clip a larger object or content renderer to a specific
							 onscreen viewport.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_window" value="69">
			<description>
				 A top level window with no title or border.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_extended" value="70">
			<description>
				 means that the role for this item is known, but not
							 included in the core enumeration. Deprecated since 2.24.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_header" value="71">
			<description>
				 An object that serves as a document header.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_footer" value="72">
			<description>
				 An object that serves as a document footer.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_paragraph" value="73">
			<description>
				 An object which is contains a single paragraph of
							 text content. See also ATSPI_ROLE_TEXT.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_ruler" value="74">
			<description>
				 An object which describes margins and tab stops, etc.
							 for text objects which it controls (should have
							 ATSPI_RELATION_CONTROLLER_FOR relation to such).

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_application" value="75">
			<description>
				 An object corresponding to the toplevel accessible
							 of an application, which may contain ATSPI_ROLE_FRAME objects or other
							 accessible objects. Children of objects with the ATSPI_ROLE_DESKTOP_FRAME role
							 are generally ATSPI_ROLE_APPLICATION objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_autocomplete" value="76">
			<description>
				 The object is a dialog or list containing items
							 for insertion into an entry widget, for instance a list of words for
							 completion of a text entry.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_editbar" value="77">
			<description>
				 The object is an editable text object in a toolbar.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_embedded" value="78">
			<description>
				 The object is an embedded component container.  This
							 role is a "grouping" hint that the contained objects share a context
							 which is different from the container in which this accessible is
							 embedded. In particular, it is used for some kinds of document embedding,
							 and for embedding of out-of-process component, "panel applets", etc.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_entry" value="79">
			<description>
				 The object is a component whose textual content may be
							 entered or modified by the user, provided ATSPI_STATE_EDITABLE is present.
							 A readonly ATSPI_ROLE_ENTRY object (i.e. where ATSPI_STATE_EDITABLE is
							 not present) implies a read-only 'text field' in a form, as opposed to a
							 title, label, or caption.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_chart" value="80">
			<description>
				 The object is a graphical depiction of quantitative data.
							 It may contain multiple subelements whose attributes and/or description
							 may be queried to obtain both the  quantitative data and information about
							 how the data is being presented. The ATSPI_LABELLED_BY relation is
							 particularly important in interpreting objects of this type, as is the
							 accessible description property. See ATSPI_ROLE_CAPTION.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_caption" value="81">
			<description>
				 The object contains descriptive information, usually
							 textual, about another user interface element such as a table, chart, or
							 image.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_frame" value="82">
			<description>
				 The object is a visual frame or container which
							 contains a view of document content.  Document frames may occur within
							 another Document instance, in which case the second document may be
							 said to be embedded in the containing instance.  HTML frames are often
							 ATSPI_ROLE_DOCUMENT_FRAME:  Either this object, or a singleton descendant,
							 should implement the org.a11y.atspi.Document interface.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_heading" value="83">
			<description>
				 The object serves as a heading for content which
							 follows it in a document. The 'heading level' of the heading, if
							 availabe,  may be obtained by       querying the object's attributes.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_page" value="84">
			<description>
				 The object is a containing instance which encapsulates a
							 page of information. ATSPI_ROLE_PAGE is used in documents and content which
							 support a paginated navigation model.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_section" value="85">
			<description>
				 The object is a containing instance of document content
							 which constitutes a particular 'logical' section of the document.  The
							 type of content within a section, and the nature of the section division
							 itself, may be obtained by querying the object's attributes.  Sections
							 may be nested.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_redundant_object" value="86">
			<description>
				 The object is redundant with another object in
							 the hierarchy, and is exposed for purely technical reasons.  Objects of
							 this role should be ignored by clients, if they are encountered at all.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_form" value="87">
			<description>
				 The object is a containing instance of document content
							 which has within it components with which the user can interact in order
							 to input information; i.e. the object is a container for pushbuttons,
							 comboboxes, text input fields, and other 'GUI' components. ATSPI_ROLE_FORM
							 should not, in general, be used for toplevel GUI containers or dialogs,
							 but should be reserved for 'GUI' containers which occur within document
							 content, for instance within Web documents, presentations, or text
							 documents.  Unlike other GUI containers and dialogs which occur inside
							 application instances, ATSPI_ROLE_FORM containers' components are
							 associated with the current document, rather than the current foreground
							 application or viewer instance.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_link" value="88">
			<description>
				 The object is a hypertext anchor, i.e. a "link" in a
							 hypertext document.  Such objects are distinct from 'inline' content
							 which may also use the Hypertext/Hyperlink interfaces to indicate
							 the range/location within a text object where an inline or embedded object
							 lies.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_input_method_window" value="89">
			<description>
				 The object is a window or similar viewport
							 which is used to allow composition or input of a 'complex character',
							 in other words it is an "input method window".

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_table_row" value="90">
			<description>
				 A row in a table.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_tree_item" value="91">
			<description>
				 An object that represents an element of a tree.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_spreadsheet" value="92">
			<description>
				 A document frame which contains a
							 spreadsheet.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_presentation" value="93">
			<description>
				 A document frame which contains a
							 presentation or slide content.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_text" value="94">
			<description>
				 A document frame which contains textual content,
							 such as found in a word processing application.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_web" value="95">
			<description>
				 A document frame which contains HTML or other
							 markup suitable for display in a web browser.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_document_email" value="96">
			<description>
				 A document frame which contains email content
							 to be displayed or composed either in plain text or HTML.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_comment" value="97">
			<description>
				 An object found within a document and designed to
							 present a comment, note, or other annotation. In some cases, this object
							 might not be visible until activated.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_list_box" value="98">
			<description>
				 A non-collapsible list of choices the user can select from.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_grouping" value="99">
			<description>
				 A group of related widgets. This group typically has a label.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_image_map" value="100">
			<description>
				 An image map object. Usually a graphic with multiple
								hotspots, where each hotspot can be activated resulting in the loading of
								another document or section of a document.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_notification" value="101">
			<description>
				 A transitory object designed to present a
								message to the user, typically at the desktop level rather than inside a
								particular application.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_info_bar" value="102">
			<description>
				 An object designed to present a message to the user
								within an existing window.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_level_bar" value="103">
			<description>
				 A bar that serves as a level indicator to, for
								instance, show the strength of a password or the state of a battery. Since: 2.8

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_title_bar" value="104">
			<description>
				 A bar that serves as the title of a window or a
								dialog. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_block_quote" value="105">
			<description>
				 An object which contains a text section
								that is quoted from another source.  Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_audio" value="106">
			<description>
				 An object which represents an audio
								element. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_video" value="107">
			<description>
				 An object which represents a video
								element. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_definition" value="108">
			<description>
				 A definition of a term or concept. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_article" value="109">
			<description>
				 A section of a page that consists of a
								composition that forms an independent part of a document, page, or
								site. Examples: A blog entry, a news story, a forum post. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_landmark" value="110">
			<description>
				 A region of a web page intended as a
								navigational landmark. This is designed to allow Assistive
								Technologies to provide quick navigation among key regions within a
								document. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_log" value="111">
			<description>
				 A text widget or container holding log content, such
								as chat history and error logs. In this role there is a
								relationship between the arrival of new items in the log and the
								reading order. The log contains a meaningful sequence and new
								information is added only to the end of the log, not at arbitrary
								points. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_marquee" value="112">
			<description>
				 A container where non-essential information
								changes frequently. Common usages of marquee include stock tickers
								and ad banners. The primary difference between a marquee and a log
								is that logs usually have a meaningful order or sequence of
								important content changes. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_math" value="113">
			<description>
				 A text widget or container that holds a mathematical
								expression. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_rating" value="114">
			<description>
				 A widget whose purpose is to display a rating,
								such as the number of stars associated with a song in a media
								player. Objects of this role should also implement
								the Value interface. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_timer" value="115">
			<description>
				 An object containing a numerical counter which
								indicates an amount of elapsed time from a start point, or the time
								remaining until an end point. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_static" value="116">
			<description>
				 A generic non-container object whose purpose is to display
								a brief amount of information to the user and whose role is known by the
								implementor but lacks semantic value for the user. Examples in which
								ATSPI_ROLE_STATIC is appropriate include the message displayed in a message
								box and an image used as an alternative means to display text.
								ATSPI_ROLE_STATIC should not be applied to widgets which are traditionally
								interactive, objects which display a significant amount of content, or any
								object which has an accessible relation pointing to another object. The
								displayed information, as a general rule, should be exposed through the
								accessible name of the object. For labels which describe another widget, see
								ATSPI_ROLE_LABEL. For text views, see ATSPI_ROLE_TEXT. For generic
								containers, see ATSPI_ROLE_PANEL. For objects whose role is not known by the
								implementor, see ATSPI_ROLE_UNKNOWN. Since: 2.16.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_math_fraction" value="117">
			<description>
				 An object that represents a mathematical fraction. Since: 2.16.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_math_root" value="118">
			<description>
				 An object that represents a mathematical expression
								displayed with a radical. Since: 2.16.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_subscript" value="119">
			<description>
				 An object that contains text that is displayed as a
								subscript. Since: 2.16.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_superscript" value="120">
			<description>
				 An object that contains text that is displayed as a
								superscript. Since: 2.16.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_description_list" value="121">
			<description>
				 An object that represents a list of term-value
								groups. A term-value group represents an individual description and consist
								of one or more names (ATSPI_ROLE_DESCRIPTION_TERM) followed by one or more
								values (ATSPI_ROLE_DESCRIPTION_VALUE). For each list, there should not be
								more than one group with the same term name. Since: 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_description_term" value="122">
			<description>
				 An object that represents a term or phrase
								with a corresponding definition. Since: 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_description_value" value="123">
			<description>
				 An object that represents the description,
								definition, or value of a term. Since: 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_footnote" value="124">
			<description>
				 An object that contains the text of a footnote. Since: 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_content_deletion" value="125">
			<description>
				 Content previously deleted or proposed to be
								deleted, e.g. in revision history or a content view providing suggestions
								from reviewers. Since: 2.34.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_content_insertion" value="126">
			<description>
				 Content previously inserted or proposed to be
								inserted, e.g. in revision history or a content view providing suggestions
								from reviewers. Since: 2.34.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_mark" value="127">
			<description>
				 A run of content that is marked or highlighted, such as for
								reference purposes, or to call it out as having a special purpose. If the
								marked content has an associated section in the document elaborating on the
								reason for the mark, then an ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS relation should be used on the mark
								to point to that associated section. In addition, the reciprocal relation
								ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS_FOR should be used on the associated content section
								to point back to the mark. See the GetRelationSet method. Since: 2.36.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_suggestion" value="128">
			<description>
				 A container for content that is called out as a
								proposed change from the current version of the document, such as by a reviewer of
								the content. An object with this role should include children with
								ATSPI_ROLE_CONTENT_DELETION and/or ATSPI_ROLE_CONTENT_INSERTION, in any order, to
								indicate what the actual change is. Since: 2.36

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_role_push_button_menu" value="129">
			<description>
				 A specialized push button to open a menu. Since: 2.46
			</description>
		</item>
	</enum>
	<enum dbus_type="u" name="relation">
		<item name="atspi_relation_null" value="0">
			<description>
				 Not a meaningful relationship; clients should not
							normally encounter this value.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_label_for" value="1">
			<description>
				 Object is a label for one or more other objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_labelled_by" value="2">
			<description>
				 Object is labelled by one or more other
							objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_controller_for" value="3">
			<description>
				 Object is an interactive object which
							modifies the state, onscreen location, or other attributes of one or more
							target objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_controlled_by" value="4">
			<description>
				 Object state, position, etc. is
							modified/controlled by user interaction with one or more other objects.
							For instance a viewport or scroll pane may be ATSPI_RELATION_CONTROLLED_BY
							scrollbars.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_member_of" value="5">
			<description>
				 Object has a grouping relationship (e.g. 'same
							group as') to one or more other objects.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_tooltip_for" value="6">
			<description>
				 Object is a tooltip associated with another
							object.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_node_child_of" value="7">
			<description>
				 Object is a child of the target.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_node_parent_of" value="8">
			<description>
				 Object is a parent of the target.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_extended" value="9">
			<description>
				 Used to indicate that a relationship exists, but
						 its type is not specified in the enumeration.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_flows_to" value="10">
			<description>
				 Object renders content which flows logically to
							 another object. For instance, text in a paragraph may flow to another
							 object which is not the 'next sibling' in the accessibility hierarchy.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_flows_from" value="11">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_FLOWS_TO.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_subwindow_of" value="12">
			<description>
				 Object is visually and semantically considered
							 a subwindow of another object, even though it is not the object's child.
							 Useful when dealing with embedded applications and other cases where the
							 widget hierarchy does not map cleanly to the onscreen presentation.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_embeds" value="13">
			<description>
				 Similar to ATSPI_RELATION_SUBWINDOW_OF, but
							 specifically used for cross-process embedding.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_embedded_by" value="14">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_EMBEDS. Used to
							 denote content rendered by embedded renderers that live in a separate process
							 space from the embedding context.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_popup_for" value="15">
			<description>
				 Denotes that the object is a transient window or
							 frame associated with another onscreen object. Similar to ATSPI_TOOLTIP_FOR,
							 but more general. Useful for windows which are technically toplevels
							 but which, for one or more reasons, do not explicitly cause their
							 associated window to lose 'window focus'. Creation of an ATSPI_ROLE_WINDOW
							 object with the ATSPI_RELATION_POPUP_FOR relation usually requires
							 some presentation action on the part of assistive technology clients,
							 even though the previous toplevel ATSPI_ROLE_FRAME object may still be
							 the active window.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_parent_window_of" value="16">
			<description>
				 This is the reciprocal relation to
							 ATSPI_RELATION_POPUP_FOR.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_description_for" value="17">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_DESCRIBED_BY.
							 Indicates that this object provides descriptive information about the target
							 object(s). See also ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS_FOR and ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_FOR.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_described_by" value="18">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_DESCRIPTION_FOR.
							 Indicates that one or more target objects provide descriptive information
							 about this object. This relation type is most appropriate for information
							 that is not essential as its presentation may be user-configurable and/or
							 limited to an on-demand mechanism such as an assistive technology command.
							 For brief, essential information such as can be found in a widget's on-screen
							 label, use ATSPI_RELATION_LABELLED_BY. For an on-screen error message, use
							 ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_MESSAGE. For lengthy extended descriptive information
							 contained in an on-screen object, consider using ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS as
							 assistive technologies may provide a means for the user to navigate to
							 objects containing detailed descriptions so that their content can be more
							 closely reviewed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_details" value="19">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS_FOR. Indicates
							 that this object has a detailed or extended description, the contents of
							 which can be found in the target object(s). This relation type is most
							 appropriate for information that is sufficiently lengthy as to make
							 navigation to the container of that information desirable. For less verbose
							 information suitable for announcement only, see ATSPI_RELATION_DESCRIBED_BY.
							 If the detailed information describes an error condition,
							 ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_FOR should be used instead.  Since 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_details_for" value="20">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_DETAILS. Indicates
							 that this object provides a detailed or extended description about the target
							 object(s). See also ATSPI_RELATION_DESCRIPTION_FOR and ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_FOR.
							 Since 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_error_message" value="21">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_FOR.
							 Indicates that this object has one or more errors, the nature of which is
							 described in the contents of the target object(s). Objects that have this
							 relation type should also contain ATSPI_STATE_INVALID_ENTRY when their
							 GetState method is called.  Since: 2.26.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_relation_error_for" value="22">
			<description>
				 Reciprocal of ATSPI_RELATION_ERROR_MESSAGE.
							 Indicates that this object contains an error message describing an invalid
							 condition in the target object(s). Since: 2.26.
			</description>
		</item>
	</enum>
	<enum dbus_type="i" name="state">
		<item name="atspi_state_invalid" value="0">
			<description>
				 Indicates an invalid state - probably an error
							condition.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_active" value="1">
			<description>
				 Indicates a window is currently the active window, or
							an object is the active subelement within a container or table. ATSPI_STATE_ACTIVE
							should not be used for objects which have ATSPI_STATE_FOCUSABLE or
							ATSPI_STATE_SELECTABLE: Those objects should use
							ATSPI_STATE_FOCUSED and ATSPI_STATE_SELECTED respectively.
							ATSPI_STATE_ACTIVE is a means to indicate that an object which is not
							focusable and not selectable is the currently-active item within its
							parent container.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_armed" value="2">
			<description>
				 Indicates that the object is armed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_busy" value="3">
			<description>
				 Indicates the current object is busy, i.e. onscreen
							representation is in the process of changing, or the object is
							temporarily unavailable for interaction due to activity already in progress.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_checked" value="4">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is currently checked.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_collapsed" value="5">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is collapsed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_defunct" value="6">
			<description>
				 Indicates that this object no longer has a valid
							backing widget (for instance, if its peer object has been destroyed).

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_editable" value="7">
			<description>
				 Indicates the user can change the contents of this
							object.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_enabled" value="8">
			<description>
				 Indicates that this object is enabled, i.e. that it
							currently reflects some application state. Objects that are "greyed out"
							may lack this state, and may lack the ATSPI_STATE_SENSITIVE if direct
							user interaction cannot cause them to acquire ATSPI_STATE_ENABLED.
							See ATSPI_STATE_SENSITIVE.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_expandable" value="9">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object allows progressive
							disclosure of its children.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_expanded" value="10">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is expanded.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_focusable" value="11">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object can accept keyboard focus,
							 which means all events resulting from typing on the keyboard will
							 normally be passed to it when it has focus.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_focused" value="12">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object currently has the keyboard
							 focus.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_has_tooltip" value="13">
			<description>
				 Indicates that the object has an associated
							 tooltip.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_horizontal" value="14">
			<description>
				 Indicates the orientation of this object is
							 horizontal.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_iconified" value="15">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is minimized and is
							 represented only by an icon.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_modal" value="16">
			<description>
				 Indicates something must be done with this object
							 before the user can interact with an object in a different window.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_multi_line" value="17">
			<description>
				 Indicates this (text) object can contain multiple
							 lines of text.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_multiselectable" value="18">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object allows more than one of
							 its children to be selected at the same time, or in the case of text
							 objects, that the object supports non-contiguous text selections.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_opaque" value="19">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object paints every pixel within its
							 rectangular region. It also indicates an alpha value of unity, if it
							 supports alpha blending.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_pressed" value="20">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is currently pressed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_resizable" value="21">
			<description>
				 Indicates the size of this object's size is not
							 fixed.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_selectable" value="22">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is the child of an object
							 that allows its children to be selected and that this child is one of
							 those children that can be selected.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_selected" value="23">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is the child of an object that
							 allows its children to be selected and that this child is one of those
							 children that has been selected.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_sensitive" value="24">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is sensitive, e.g. to user
							 interaction. ATSPI_STATE_SENSITIVE usually accompanies.
							 ATSPI_STATE_ENABLED for user-actionable controls, but may be found in the
							 absence of ATSPI_STATE_ENABLED if the current visible state of the control
							 is "disconnected" from the application state.  In such cases, direct user
							 interaction can often result in the object gaining ATSPI_STATE_SENSITIVE,
							 for instance if a user makes an explicit selection using an object whose
							 current state is ambiguous or undefined. See ATSPI_STATE_ENABLED,
							 ATSPI_STATE_INDETERMINATE.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_showing" value="25">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object, the object's parent, the
							 object's parent's parent, and so on, are all 'shown' to the end-user,
							 i.e. subject to "exposure" if blocking or obscuring objects do not
							 interpose between this object and the top of the window stack.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_single_line" value="26">
			<description>
				 Indicates this (text) object can contain only a
							 single line of text.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_stale" value="27">
			<description>
				 Indicates that the information returned for this object
							 may no longer be synchronized with the application state.  This can occur
							 if the object has ATSPI_STATE_TRANSIENT, and can also occur towards the
							 end of the object peer's lifecycle.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_transient" value="28">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is transient.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_vertical" value="29">
			<description>
				 Indicates the orientation of this object is vertical;
							 for example this state may appear on such objects as scrollbars, text
							 objects (with vertical text flow), separators, etc.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_visible" value="30">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object is visible, e.g. has been
							 explicitly marked for exposure to the user. ATSPI_STATE_VISIBLE is no
							 guarantee that the object is actually unobscured on the screen, only that
							 it is 'potentially' visible, barring obstruction, being scrolled or clipped
							 out of the field of view, or having an ancestor container that has not yet
							 made visible. A widget is potentially onscreen if it has both
							 ATSPI_STATE_VISIBLE and ATSPI_STATE_SHOWING. The absence of
							 ATSPI_STATE_VISIBLE and ATSPI_STATE_SHOWING is
							 semantically equivalent to saying that an object is 'hidden'.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_manages_descendants" value="31">
			<description>
				 Indicates that "active-descendant-changed"
							 event is sent when children become 'active' (i.e. are selected or
							 navigated to onscreen).  Used to prevent need to enumerate all children
							 in very large containers, like tables. The presence of
							 ATSPI_STATE_MANAGES_DESCENDANTS is an indication to the client that the
							 children should not, and need not, be enumerated by the client.
							 Objects implementing this state are expected to provide relevant state
							 notifications to listening clients, for instance notifications of
							 visibility changes and activation of their contained child objects, without
							 the client having previously requested references to those children.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_indeterminate" value="32">
			<description>
				 Indicates that a check box or other boolean
							 indicator is in a state other than checked or not checked.  This
							 usually means that the boolean value reflected or controlled by the
							 object does not apply consistently to the entire current context.
							 For example, a checkbox for the "Bold" attribute of text may have
							 ATSPI_STATE_INDETERMINATE if the currently selected text contains a mixture
							 of weight attributes. In many cases interacting with a
							 ATSPI_STATE_INDETERMINATE object will cause the context's corresponding
							 boolean attribute to be homogenized, whereupon the object will lose
							 ATSPI_STATE_INDETERMINATE and a corresponding state-changed event will be
							 fired.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_required" value="33">
			<description>
				 Indicates that user interaction with this object is
							 'required' from the user, for instance before completing the
							 processing of a form.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_truncated" value="34">
			<description>
				 Indicates that an object's onscreen content
							 is truncated, e.g. a text value in a spreadsheet cell.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_animated" value="35">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object's visual representation is
							 dynamic, not static. This state may be applied to an object during an
							 animated 'effect' and be removed from the object once its visual
							 representation becomes static. Some applications, notably content viewers,
							 may not be able to detect all kinds of animated content.  Therefore the
							 absence of this state should not be taken as
							 definitive evidence that the object's visual representation is
							 static; this state is advisory.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_invalid_entry" value="36">
			<description>
				 This object has indicated an error condition
							 due to failure of input validation.  For instance, a form control may
							 acquire this state in response to invalid or malformed user input.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_supports_autocompletion" value="37">
			<description>
				 This state indicates that the object
							 in question implements some form of typeahead or
							 pre-selection behavior whereby entering the first character of one or more
							 sub-elements causes those elements to scroll into view or become
							 selected. Subsequent character input may narrow the selection further as
							 long as one or more sub-elements match the string. This state is normally
							 only useful and encountered on objects that implement AtspiSelection.
							 In some cases the typeahead behavior may result in full or partial
							 completion of the data in the input field, in which case
							 these input events may trigger text-changed events from the source.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_selectable_text" value="38">
			<description>
				 This state indicates that the object in
							 question supports text selection. It should only be exposed on objects
							 which implement the AtspiText interface, in order to distinguish this state
							 from ATSPI_STATE_SELECTABLE, which infers that the object in question is a
							 selectable child of an object which implements AtspiSelection. While
							 similar, text selection and subelement selection are distinct operations.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_is_default" value="39">
			<description>
				 This state indicates that the object in question is
							 the 'default' interaction object in a dialog, i.e. the one that gets
							 activated if the user presses "Enter" when the dialog is initially
							 posted.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_visited" value="40">
			<description>
				 This state indicates that the object (typically a
							 hyperlink) has already been activated or invoked, with the result that
							 some backing data has been downloaded or rendered.

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_checkable" value="41">
			<description>
				 Indicates this object has the potential to
							 be checked, such as a checkbox or toggle-able table cell. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_has_popup" value="42">
			<description>
				 Indicates that the object has a popup
							 context menu or sub-level menu which may or may not be
							 showing. This means that activation renders conditional content.
							 Note that ordinary tooltips are not considered popups in this
							 context. Since: 2.12

			</description>
		</item>
		<item name="atspi_state_read_only" value="43">
			<description>
				 Indicates that an object which is ENABLED and
							 SENSITIVE has a value which can be read, but not modified, by the
							 user. Since: 2.16
			</description>
		</item>
	</enum>
</enums>
